{"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Which%20river%20flows%20through%20the%20Scottish%20city%20of%20Glasgow%3F","correct_answer":"Clyde","incorrect_answers":["Tay","Dee","Tweed"]},{"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What%20is%20the%20defining%20characteristic%20of%20someone%20who%20is%20described%20as%20hirsute%3F","correct_answer":"Hairy","incorrect_answers":["Rude","Funny","Tall"]},{"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"A%20doctor%20with%20a%20PhD%20is%20a%20doctor%20of%20what%3F","correct_answer":"Philosophy","incorrect_answers":["Psychology","Phrenology","Physical%20Therapy"]},{"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Which%20of%20the%20following%20buildings%20is%20example%20of%20a%20structure%20primarily%20built%20in%20the%20Art%20Deco%20architectural%20style%3F","correct_answer":"Niagara%20Mohawk%20Building","incorrect_answers":["Taipei%20101","One%20Detroit%20Center","Westendstrasse%201"]},{"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What%20country%20saw%20a%20world%20record%20315%20million%20voters%20turn%20out%20for%20elections%20on%20May%2020%2C%201991%3F","correct_answer":"India","incorrect_answers":["United%20States%20of%20America","Soviet%20Union","Poland"]},{"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Which%20of%20the%20General%20Mills%20Corporation%27s%20monster%20cereals%20was%20the%20last%20to%20be%20released%20in%20the%201970%27s%3F","correct_answer":"Fruit%20Brute","incorrect_answers":["Count%20Chocula","Franken%20Berry","Boo-Berry"]},{"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What%20was%20Mountain%20Dew%27s%20original%20slogan%3F","correct_answer":"Yahoo%21%20Mountain%20Dew...%20It%27ll%20tickle%20your%20innards%21","incorrect_answers":["Give%20Me%20A%20Dew","Do%20The%20Dew","Get%27%20that%20barefoot%20feelin%27%20drinkin%27%20Mountain%20Dew"]},{"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Which%20slogan%20did%20the%20fast%20food%20company%2C%20McDonald%27s%2C%20use%20before%20their%20%22I%27m%20Lovin%27%20It%22%20slogan%3F","correct_answer":"We%20Love%20to%20See%20You%20Smile","incorrect_answers":["Why%20Pay%20More%21%3F","Have%20It%20Your%20Way","Making%20People%20Happy%20Through%20Food"]},{"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What%20was%20the%20original%20name%20of%20the%20search%20engine%20%22Google%22%3F","correct_answer":"BackRub","incorrect_answers":["CatMassage","SearchPro","Netscape%20Navigator"]},{"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Which%20of%20these%20words%20means%20%22idle%20spectator%22%3F","correct_answer":"Gongoozler","incorrect_answers":["Gossypiboma","Jentacular","Meupareunia"]}]}